business software engineering region the
podcast for professional developers of the
we badass idea video that map
essie video is by-the-bye that computer
from chablis software magazine online a
computer thereby
sluis apple recipe service video is
brought to you by bringo
i think that your premium system xs oil
change vulnerable way lucas moura
theory and looked and bring two three
companions
humor bring two payments dot com slash
that region
[Music]
hello everyone this is family proposal
for engineering radio live the michael
feathers
michael furthermore is the punder of ars
traffic a research and conveyance
whereby you here now with msi order of
wording effectively with legacy kap and
legacy code is the top i al far as i
radio podcast
hello michael welcome to the show
michael my first question for you what
is to live cito
men the sun ving week om livesey is er
een meisje hungry after experts
disco so well nice see how it should be there
such a brush miko stories
jerry definition logistics old wood away
and then so sour away is those codes for the
dank of his maria's
where we  with of that big brother or your
father function guy on heaven's
insight-app base with fire from van moore
those types in russians becomes co2 pattern
uniformity
so essential action codes toyotas
and reason why did a dos bicos a dead
star slope homemade testing in place
from co2 much much you change
and then it would already I socialize
reference with corn for your frame
identical down side to side steps and
trash out some people change my mind is
trico sirens tea for my and styling
power
but like that yeah sorry guys that definition
but marino-city the texture definition
bright chili peppers
so a huh anything to push age
necessarily facts to the
some people viewed from i thumpy
yesterday and and and more to go eat
at praying so a retest and
usa gets ready show and immediately see
this is red mustache it's just monda from the
shy guy fact it's deadly shadows ko's
type jewelry iphone cases of that now
really red devils my car mini wifi for
3 buttons they also the koran glasdoor that
is laughing themselves on the crassula
reach service tanks where  Iranian of
the polio here become imogen real have
you have what see then hate was the
tanks to aim coaching magnetic
holder can you the pen the week and then would so
yes so still not so clear in
invent it in that the girl tinkebell
queens to intertwine are words
legacy of course overhead instead
etienne something that's how i don't you
we they showed you emply samsung and
build quality praised his you this have
common in the mystery so then tram itself
because that is yeti formed venture themselves
already match report is in the no other
in the battle with a workshop there a
snail shell low cm at the station that
has no exotic congress nederweert
we the acknowledgment of the show definitions
and using your definition of receding you
that football park estimado how much cold
in the world you think is it legacy
but we had to we here is name is
marlies
highlighter that link sustainable by
system of johan microlife and or my
book for take orders on
could sometimes to see that these people can your
mother to talk so your on now further
so missionary [ __ ] a certain way
a mercenary  iphone 3g bugs in
europe so to portugal cyprus and the
queen was cases but my photos
inside why you're supposed to your
doctor john medley and note that we
have people swish and the there of you
becomes there section gas
you see sit I do da da da but boring
towards we positioning of chow chow
mexico the red nose the cold dual of
street legacy shall I my tea with
theres a new codebase
dare throw this salt through all religion
yes how is this of your bed show week so well
I for start with a soldiers you
and your
jumpscares care in the by medical company
and who goes the theory of gotico and
in whisky cashmere ftw threw the
body
burberry online guide by the way ipod
would maybe was and who very large
and the of pack broader replaced and
went bags for your website situation
it is an online much that are your team
see we threw in schiedam and record is
a short high power battery technology
software so since 10 euro that caught the
legacy code is getting better
her including system earth no
relatively new system ecostar
industries is moving  forward and were
getting better and testing en wefact
remorse justice cms en unreadable
onno hoes the other way around chemistry science
social
future research as many of these tree
files pollution to the station and who
the door is the fire wire
in question mini string as a last few
photos of lamborghini house of a cupboard
well this driver
greengiving share a magic
polypeptides china understand and if you
win privacy sammy outside young from
the start
credo 3 those awards and why factory
devil paul jacks the week was gracious us
mine with an organizations on the
shadow side shows all kinds of links and
the suzie awake care
that does not yet exist and three teenagers and
difference between different paradise and programming
and the legacy they
create and for simple is also legacy
different from procedural legacy of
functional legacy oh my sweet reaction
flexie you're my car service to lay
see do you think there address hi sander fest
judged decorate proving' johanna
maria the libertarian in succeeds wind blows
orientations with a
tumblr and then thinks and respect and lord
of the young
wardenburg down town has been reactive
two situations  the finals of potassium two
when will my car foundation
just the idea so anyway home betty
and encapsulate red keep it in your
application by inkthemes.com
samsung note station always new audio
a deep put your application
so the worksheet a screenshot an
iphone too cold so
marianne him ingredient and spring
prostheses yes new york rome teletigers is
there the rai lifeboat his pi another
jello
the tanks most osteoarthritis on the stones
specifically angro
beyond also rest of europe and thereby
ideal windsurfing
lure that chunk a symmetry that and
just kind think in terms of shows was
active orientation
jeroen have new forest t promise and
physiology that boy had the risk
so is with a photo for function notice
that make it easier to maintain
functional cold I know that so there
you keep seeing playing crafting is such a and
I had to rod of you went grey knife or
favorite codebase a doctor md of choco
days after high magic sherlock holmes
european kings wiper it so I give
hefty with big boys or
but actually a courgette mind you surer
rohde  slipper scoop from experts
seo sang woo you haven't seen in a huge
multi-line account functional systems
gets really know how they would be a
younger and get to tango even more for
more more than per rise like my car
service of reactive programming because
i do nep codebase is whether that now on
airlines
in the moor yes perth so there is from
yvette study coach order of marina we now
lukaku history industrial something is a
medicine graphite mass from roy dawkins
that faster
you are me black shoes nike sony's
with sleek design and
star of David of copies a cup honey in
state still
youtube trailer online prins mos der
mark louis carrisford technology
research programmes
sarina versions of microsoft site so
great technique guard and sizes small to
which v40 grading small piece together
to my first week and climbing in the pantry
charlie give you my mother sam situation
to dab and men with the handsome kation
game so
succeed gerard there already could you push
large and complex idea internet store
bonus was a in charles
love at the legacy coach  shofar of
English mania interpreting belly the skills and
social networking and legacy co-teaching
original legacy code is harder than
working in greenfield project
yes thinking so and he think it's an
interesting thing for secretly serious is
it grigio project your database master
from scratch
maxims sound which the hunger polar
translation
dare I him later in legacy code go
[ __ ] night in bath and beach dress of
the modify fingers that along to
support foil and now I have a
bit forward texts and people start
can of the votes
m so in the or more download page in
english and assisting
posters two new testament uncle
santoni wife was absolutely mean so
that mina juni the of skills to work and
and greenfield project for his selection
projector to an idea of ​​tools that you
approach problems in the dow there is it is
a tool be it lightly of pablo aimar
solid of touring so stupid idea of
skills with I dissing musts come and
my name is who didn't know how younger
voice
arco and
not a know what you monster outcast
excelsior were range support my
linkedin tomorrow legacy code grey'
training family what I know
pedigree code applications but of the
politics user you time new the slide 2
slide
control and a now infection of yes
of course not even with a constraint or
well that to support them of so yes by the
of skills as her life in a day
the jai lai lai much using a working with
legacy code diskant a bit
and better greenfield to fell per
which which makes sense itenc
no so would we your factor in London
was and so yes with suppose you you're
doing the legacy projectmenu for the
fourth time
how do you get better and it be our
practicing in the codebase is itself harder
and exercises you could places my the
ortec nothing that you can practice recognizable
legacy koala blooming in your project
oh I'm doing it now already a new series of
those use various exercises you get people
to trial version of technical people
of in you take view this exercise their
stories chain application
hi ya guys so ham' defense operation
why so sorry
mobile applications on using an exercise
I think that thing about a already knew the
technicians at page level your belly of you
against well every time for you not ebay
hand do sanitizing response theology
banks bankrupt idea  to both the box
rather show
crash and a CD series practical missing
since your existing applications within
its ya know when you there is nothing
like the page officielle in basement
jaxx curve and then so massively this is the
old finger hd of posterior dodici of of
your voice of god
and then you are james yeah they practicing
exam codebase is be like practicing
slim another country
you can practice on things at ultimate
sweetheart does anyone want paris
just not water sewer responsibility for
a cold bath yes msn address lydia shows on
you such a headlight came when you open
source two little beasts those people hey what
for them eh yes this is my two b's mega
big thousand rosemary january in an
architect in time verbs
hi an organ works on some architecture
in situations jesse
to some people look down on legacy
projection want on a dvd mss les cool
or maybe islam used one thing sms
prestigious tank greenfield project be
giving back realistic is theres a trick
en ador group cidade oliebol
what I said was a rocky mountain
coaching around know how people
organizations that us everything what north in
sentosa and the britten van der es gibt uw
star nu projects all the time you know
de stad theme song release van mijn bias
perspectiva 3 de body workout er is not
system bottles
so yes give you three kinds of
bradley next to her and recognize how the
board and i hope dat office mask is
wel van [ __ ] you happy toy signal i see
this work thinking in over optimizer
very demanding en exploratorium
targeting de deur wanneer de stinkokken
sram xo
en is in panty motivée developers bij
offering them a combination of sunlight
i work and sam green field work or is
that no time een keer bij mij op
instagram posture sitting in central so
sorry for the us and china baby belly ring
die van jason set inch mini
application you were great work and now
his widow spoilery can now new
sociobiology at a crossroads everything was
articles bij budget maier je medication
k yes professional century
hereby rafting conductor airco when I
sixteen system on fire
but your man of sixty wants you and
coaching system system and then again no
wire for start free trial lesson to
so new members chewbacca's orientation
a wonderfully warm bath thing that showed
you software engineering
content the gimme that make your in these
changes marco further away
samsung rather now videogames
energy desk mc chucky modifiers class
rodenhuis
to tony medicine and head' another
spanish 322
working still red queen fashion
downgrade char that water approach
name is me of a river well your baby
clothes new queen firefly
in and chronicles not system education
so I sign microbial became access all
the time go critters and are three the
codebase is there indeed an earlier of
monopolies that of and you can there a base
for changing the the class
jesse must you thing is a legacy
project the roos and greenfield activities
i sometimes you and I now code and ipad 3
forties of social networking in the
green field hall along the steek green
f you wish you so ham' areas of your
codebase array that leak test annually sun
along the work of so in green projects
also help figure out how the geniuses ho
kyungri wit agree then maybe stop
this listing toilet jets in greenfield
and long ciba vision tank marwa
activities for work of features as being  or
greenfield
farmer eyed demon word project or a
legacy word project where you so such
modifications and some refactoring mark
yes think about derby media marketing
suites classnobr with a broad webservice
of frans met him have
newest rocky mountains and i morgen
software released their own time in a
few ing sociotherapy national history
once you start the routing products
some remedies implication start say
it a narrow not new features many
features symbiosis working in the context
of solitary maurice like a new york new
york with modern krugman for this is my for
but for housing to section
esther privacy of new business or
flight ii cover
yo take notice i win for miranda
a difference in for sale in a small
person at a bar
the sad annies care of all time and sss
the beams what saffron chinese is taking
care of the teams production manager
and the piri jet for three and codebase
will be your lungs rafter zipper already
confess
my that that moisture in microprocessor
only few people get to work on any
epic such a smart no time the steel
grey yes yes  that
's gross food yummy for reading
to grace' station
committee of the Grammys also okay mrs at
this point the of belt is so a
my channel switch via for a great job
you're ready
you for where the last song free dam
because you can move it anymore you can
decide the time of three beagles there was
already decided by the way for little
so he explanation at
and elliot no this is the real thing which
i knew your guitar complications
so I diggin' secretary that room show
you my that way architects in already once
a year when we young technium
a compromise the packaging that system
what 316 strasser is that as a package
sat of over i know series undertaking
you feel like your architecture of the same
architecture games tent just as if he
math cd john was as if I a
matter of lesson mechanic next on the
gradients decor touchpad
nrf times over the course on the podcast
testing
what is the relationship between then
testing and legacy code you ever and the
divine legacy code s code week old s what
me down test is where i binary badges
euro a brush
how many test arnie the hardcore  glam kim
new top model the relationship between
6 and mighty
say necessary
msc marketing is shine most
popular him division is organizations
to press that by name is actually
of direction player erase or iphone
apps answers for tess cottage and then
characters with the Finns at dorothy
single boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy
oh boy oh boy
oh  boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy
oh boy oh boy oh boy oh
boy oh boy oh james
and you who invested  co-domination
guest portal
so that handsome one for debugger place  free
north of the showroom model
nicola crash test for the debugger the
bag in your review
mike tyson sandwich of leather and
actresses and bitter of corn in whitey
graphics
entail that region why you make changes
want so high five from madam person
with a military the texel smart for
them and gradually shows
online test is what we not supported
here n dry touch audio why do nothing
that much jongerius
so is just a comb and the hardcore bases
home
your coach of drivers and political
carriers ups and the migration caesar
that way there is an oh sorry you this
one
12 from testing with changes that i make
for it tony hayward is a red cabbage with
harry jono fx and fx the setup is and
and answer to my question is 0 every
party codebase not I want a manifesto
some parts and more likely to change and
others you may know that you measure
change process of source code of the
people you
is on the software becomes partner that
important to them how do you know this
blog
okay so the top marie-josé
emotional us light please you the black
of mackeeper change and the focus and then
you  let it go do like like your
[ __ ] Sartin O' Mais and industry
Churchill Cee'd sw for James Dean something
with it
and if your product or feature coming
and ICT
here series bankrupt Maria so Peter
Empires
for service the series photos to
force anyway should be familiar this feature
is mode easy 30 liters
and then this is after
take you can Caesar by Thomas to the
Ardennes factor north of
Christmas tender and something 32 feature and
then metro station Termini White it stands
and that she knew how clothing
now the driver features Johan Italy was
a volume cold quite intense two typical
Lady Gaga sort of Bjorn
they have now to an organization that
rapes again outside see my god for
Theodorus I would you interested in
chocolaterie architect and projects
sunrise but you can also give you my
work I made this tree for the kadees and
find a no worries hopeless change over
realtime
case happy love box and then yes you
have the factory is Rebecca your nose ear
doctor Pansar location
but this sports of Bourjois seriously
protest mask over
those beautiful stripes making it recent
the everybody never what the hotspots arno
shervin send him for jay-z that full
arrivel to grab identifiers gryon
jellybean fiery red
using them feel like you to measure the
change pro new premium project in
many developers and beam
input for long time ago he together
intuition and ali is for bradley's my
[ __ ] jim lawrence van hamish circle
sudokus about you grey family
forget is and anyway is the nori process
manager version which we have all the
rest there hemmink is monique van athene
vote no more at whatsapp and in of your
fire up in march of 2015
you find of your core business point
went along with me quincy promes is quite an
active arias over engineering research
to their heart you is a technical then
you to use to pinpoint
whisky part-up there now for that last
lesson continuing story you live for nursing living
grounding new feature you a
feeling test for that features
specifically who is that I you fuji-san you
won't you like you didn't see the
approach for driving test and and in
installments  yes
the doctor s  e stuck flyers yes if your
photos timing and I can bleed something
in which a sort of when assie loves
how fence and rosings now really a
terrorist gladys who donor heart to
change things must airport I there feature
so going to exercise of in shanghai little
house so code nice north of
nickerie looks in the big for the
snow feature amaliastraat brush minus
3 well as a missionary 3 lite red and
facilities minutes door and in the
engine room china isarco the to the
glamour tess it becomes an arduino board
pharmacies the more often and download it now
white successful to antisocial
more schooling day further had to peter
bridge knowledge is but can you off need and
be with me tested in basel of mini 16
cold so expensive snails change at
cocktail bar
ride before you will get the audio of
issue that tdf a little bit
gets more like butch you the code gotta
make it easy
what is a char scepter how it will
use defense breaking hand in
leather by testing is one of my favorite
subject to an agile testing and lions
hear  the goal in view a thing and new
features it makes sense to passing tests
become part of the codebase
your be tested by logging not touch a
right day still
samsung note i introduce for is a
big tear through zazzle's iphone with
flash of label
erotic games krasinski arjuna via
the jungle went the people use to do
mother testing
is for testing system pro destroy your
magic sorry that and
a donor must something with the downey
gb enrico
the choice but winchester connections aiko
the single that I die espada lobby of
her post correct and then your shaslik
director
must you do is use torben exercise in the
code not catch with i also at home and
that chick that is back so at the
test in a planks my nose expecto
dali's on west end on this car french
art
mosa sellers in strings pkc teacher at
each evening star rider testicles and
shows i say what those codes by
partners a scribble liberta
delivers his that your music spain so
just is of warm water
tips the beam in microsens blush and
compatible depending upon the body below and you
Shirley business will be
and so the tank data social and i want you
back to find out what really means
so us and 2 bars recent production of
specification and is a for fixed and push
him the idea the family loss project
prep' leaders and maybe then i know they
change remake a European medido der bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae bae
success rate dead hasstone roof
my character li document the behavior
attention and chivalrous not chief
society is like tanning builder well and so
my vest fashion
you divide yourself a young and then change
i started  our touched and then ship
women young tasty change so the
citigo in a bar action with ratio was I
already right
this podcast i supported by light i just
now
hosting solution provider of healthcare
have pc and compliance and add that
you feel in the legs auction artery
technology diet cola i just now and
get a lady securely firewall intrusion
detection back-up disaster recovery and
vegetation
for disruption and your project an item
in a small room water comparators
and line i just now can help your section
billions this solutions and 20 who is a
business day just that you that is the
net line i just now too long
[Music]
yes how is the pain becomes and microsoft
for December and that becomes around your excel
codebase
and there view housing errors in microsoft
excel
beds team candles fix
impulse in the moor correct 2 be just a
free spreadsheet in the world
that news boxes functional that mother
fd of values ​​will review garnier
edgar edgar edgar c journal character
body butter specify the person they
should and two
hypothermia you do the pen excelsior
greyjoy I say who knows you don't know either
where you have of the family
along  those code workers from us for
pleasure working in a book from our
stars aboe bakr omar and in the week a
failure words words experience disco
music server becomes riper in the afternoon what
I sam coming down between concepts the
depth
the domain in the standard to a so the
domain is for my busy through a networks
for saxophone study standard to a is
like this the way that works don't ask me
peter and such as the business on
time doperse mind showing the standard
to a and the with it and economy between your
buttocks from the training except below
sea level t-shirt and the domain is for
operation and I said know your own new
feature you will test such a horse or the
codebase it well that for you start and I
my new feature and heforshe you go
in bloem and can i feel safe to start
doing the real programming kroon and
toddler willy out of the features instead of
still testing and a really thinks that they
workflow [ __ ] we
he knew come back to what this is what
i do for germany testing all right
is can you of it in this situation now
sorry rappers or a
we anyway of responsible for the mad
king crab changes within a codebase and
what  and really means have yet to go
pro the stock market and I of the water but
with in the demo team htc watch me so oh
my word test and youtube frinstance
in made and the buildings times a day
hout-sawyer i'm a van add your
particular area
politician didn't know showing you just
gotta find us
but do what chf sek him just for a
scrimmage I say I was necessary for
this photograph is not so you can afford
official page
offers debian responsible and
suites at ago as much as i miss the text
you
monsieur would be what more thing is quite
professional
hdcp equi linn looking for michael se
mini one piece and this fight and liking
globally kind themselves not with them fit
that bottle because there are two day
dresses you the rio de weald and grasses
minus 3 is 2
basil jasmin babushka and then plus c
address with asia with the criterion
and dead body situation ionesco the
brush and public there are domain
defense is indeed there is the fans mcqueen
images cms and building software
for and nuclear power plant of cancer
treatment facility office building
codebase is  has there interchangeable
shofar direction just a testing of
course there different forms of testing
so the the testing were talking we those little
hairs legacy codebase in live at
test before adding and feature what tests
army extreme i care unit tests
integration test performance test the
people know from i just home
performance test the alarm
in our people have a high-performance
kutcher and demi
other mostar enormous teams the driver
from china and i in oktober icing there is
a bodge bankrupt becomes when is the
water josh numbers or tram that five and
then
i know that is why why my first time
released by
spock to our excuse millions tesla have
kpn kubota about when you wish you don't
try this sort of icon
cartridges more systems mit composed
system-level
interest lars smoke session for many
changes at all and a yes of that
sympathy philippines duo tickets
new these women blogging budgeting
those yogis listening sandwich and spiders
were time
white as far away from your own min 9
hours changes
and then i took an interview what kind of
beast gingrich and and acquaintances the point
where when something great
is come on fire  the change was
to reach the greenhouses you will high-level thessaly
blythe and charlie
second dry-touch rescue of the ticker
change went along in her ep fine
sunshine suites succeed
maud he sings the high'll over the most
you really know us dollar exactly like
once amsterdam or a bad guy
ritchie led mirror good the scientist
at gaston and besides testing and always
a favor of fair use other techniques and
us in mexico spaces to not break stuff
to say zein tvv
mailchimp our starting this amazing
cursuscode reviews airco inhibition of is
so all the songs for the most part of
this review
you can tchite van get information
barbers s 10 euro to no one in which
everything about tanks in your set timings
phone number
and just wrote crush and what kind iroh
and saxophone badger testing now I said
the doctor
hi hi analogy testing same righting
testing me scraper it's also is a matter
of johnny thing is much information
chinese of bryan roy the of sources
the module can was also a transition is
on stirs in  starfleet eyeliner
hi often you can barely there white and
what I so fantastic america's
amino acids typo station tanks [ __ ]
and break down and then that we career
so simple shepherdess off that couch in
a number of lengths
is extra of pension other class and then
in domino you do you give rise to you
class and auditing star fell in that car
fast moving show now les animaux the
robot shoes not and bastiaan a huge
and sisters and I a disco and place your
efforts to the now the new approach and
projections okay now I know that take my violin
with school bags like to you guys
like using the ai-system
the branch check if I a bar necessary
tessa and
game political expensive is in her
breasts go the ghost b how support us
theory not supported with changers
authentic cappuccino where
so medior our house a that my training
and co2 and legacy codebase in the city I
language some it wanted us in medical
leo bicky whining am in the dynamic time
purchase that
remember with a gift so a string
stimulus also family of your favorite
be alive and suffering serious to
exclusive there never sparta and went you
you can 7  because left winger santing as
start samsen works on something as
digital triage new friend and shy guy
van den swirling bro i that via a
dynamic strong
mybox tv and what a cloud my friends
from countax
with thinks about it strong few years the war
of the duck little house in which co that I that
he tomorrow in dynamic
oa of yoga video naturae choose one
negative feedback and the feedback and
countries as opposed to power and claps
italy
you something terror statements stone in
the burner and working in a and so so
like you instant relief and forums is
loses juffermans
just now and mysticism between apps with
manager adjust him
norish mythology sunset failures
trillion sausage cheese ham salami and every
line care sarlat for testing and special
the first we heard a your moment
sam must start at facebook nec moe
fast and brings us at staff and we will
see what happens leder test 1 year in
one of waste of time is not yet whether I there a a
feel about that can this be
done in legacy codebase is codee and
charlie dory's this neutral country in
romantic foil samsung words words
will  we in on the icon at home not
February along what irina context ona then
with your web pages on black welkers
and grimaud theory role as an
impressively sorry my poor region
seeking types of
got had to video and my potential
loose so he had miss lily survival for
facebook right then this program so
sounds so macho software engineering is
especially when nerves
the palm is where after 20 graffiti nesh
media and were forums is megaphone
braver situations so yes logical
codebase poor audience on facebook scores
logical so busy fod do have I a
little is now 15 bridge of sighs
flagship of the boat came honey bes
6s all my channel bolts show who
you are
politics the the fingers most porn
girls that feedback wu's store
where so in testing feedback professor
person is in house week none of the
testing of silicon show working properly
but we thermal gas progressive
risk and georgi roof shapes and then
to the reader wiske both the gym duwo
[Music]
yes so good ryan livestream notez with
feedback thunder basswood in champing
yes yes so from you from your mind free
george  roda pasante ratio die
presentations
use decency of pic programmer at ing we
are of your process become juliette bag
those videos online must your mouth you feel
my car services europe code week a
training of family need any managers and
is waikiki cubes and are where the
snowwoman all universes of jean and
jeanne marie airport security manager
supply chain and gray was or something like that
parish center family sports or 35 is
a tiger ii single situation at factory
racing for a is a rising there yes it is
there support the construction where
madam mina piano
what your finger i was in a good way and
what you we not two successful would
disappear
below that stand you can texas were so
small and so at domain preferably also cee'd
out of the panty breaking region page which
is why we take you own kate in the
booked make out more testing want to make
it easier to test and define what
defense breaking news for you what is it
yes
mini when tess good evening irving's i
an app and info these young monks
in the test a warm tongue kind of video
then class network
hi is new genre yim  the scariest
the week in apps question by things your
ipod shuffle a test that bumps onto your computer
barcode with jesus and then so
boring subject number break to spanish
speaking test
the logic nationalism would a white tie
gala that
decorates like that god the risk little beast sits
smartphone fine in nice places
but my code museum organizes read
my team was another so that now know
yes lightbox actors or two of
semester old acquaintances and misrecognition
number and yes sorry
tip water and mud these things there many
words distortion lambs and I a
concrete I simple vision you never win
much match in people that for melia
know then technically your workflow naruto
risk they say they have fun shampoo
professional scenario that kind of
measurements domino day of functional and
these are chosen function b and bot a
bionic are ready jef diederen santing
there is papa brand for sander at home lay
certainly son joop and they business in san-san
things quasimodo had
young bbc necessary was china minute
iphone is become you no music and
overriding physiological meter of us is
usually between classes or this run and
over white beach of the body
some you  discover electric antique dealer
minute was a situation like that is king
samsung corby
the smartphone in rio bsv 2 and 3 are
discourse pk's
a central and about their function and can
you see them
monitor arm it is a place where we
not nice I the counter jjc big b but
eat sms who tries you the china's so
the giving where cs to you fortunately the
cold was so a what you no breaking point
knowledge that we that change your a
pharmacy relationship breakdown holiday home where
and what we so
ms and so logical and photo chemicals
increases chocolate government amc
green sea of ​​ever new iphone
symbols an extra service and those
stupid microscopic tests situation
easytape spectators on the must we
super wiper and danny no besselink
and micky there the black sea life for
production or a little longer max for
testing and stuff the scene airstrikes method
length a must especially someone
begin now places for a long time in the
chapel give the rooier
why that would my god guys this week
so long time and place with another after
a based upon you on stage
the place you the site was fine which
provides the fun things
and then there is a  sad of this good
ornament code 012 deadlines than I a bbq
chicken lodge
when tycho and with that tasmania and the
idol had properties i enjoyed hit
him the idea and let's see who is it
things the property is system of the
house that you can explore
elk i just an exam or a things
see when i knew of your day logical
choice body from someone at innax for
that routine klaas and then
rodin method is king doing some fine
iphones touch and mac is the list by
the made start extra quaestor in tony
meter we take juice bottle interface over
ride a battery packs got so heavy at
sogeti ideal I kissed her buttocks something
I could later on time i need you' they
see become was to a teenager
and in your booklet he and number of
technical team make-up murder murder
estival
what is your favorite technique to mediation
eskimos wiley applicable tank not the
most beautiful you stole my pokémons this
wrote there is a social in which were
baked where sex seekers to my
class of e-bikes pony
2014 photo and  Sebring technically with oil
bridging for or an overcome this
research is fine actually instructor
the hour distance and you must be Leica
the PC of you of camels contest
arms sturdy and Tesla just relax had
wrapped anchor and that get together to
lower the well what was that smell in circa
black for plastic sestriere Miss Mary
Nestor
for Krishna Carine for to become can you
now artificial root the cerebrospinal fluid argonauts
million apps and CMA production
project for and then Miss Bingley New
York in spoke earlier
pikemen in production buddy Holly
story you feel it is therefore you to go
in these fine arts in the language and then
thousand dollars the baby's name is a
Justin sexy neurological function of the
exactly to single chance Molly Thunder
Tiger to but daddy milk for your Honda
Jazz that must guys sorry of cash
flows YouTube tight
posts 2 so you must php and add
your and various countries reads or technique be
has the pants and this book is something
Redblue it over ten years ago
Ardor any of the technique would be move
maybe they do to ecological and are high
a site to  an idea to ecological and
sniper house in Heverlee
hello does now become I think to type okay
technological
the whipped cream curator and so you will
technical of admiral each of those
must you so states chicken that become
why we just alliance and say what you
so the station for each yotsugi
applications info desk exist your
thesis so that you we party together
articles that discount also factory spring
is sometimes on
mark the truck motor god something new
type of technology and design and was
based finance insight-app
curtly and the teams with testing the finer
things which only design gifts
sophic design can the 13th can see but
that I want something you in four teams
were that your reaction in the projector
and the firm is education
ho cheerly find
provence a test a mission vs where
even is now dead orange
defines would not so testing is sunday
secular feeling design issues and
resource coline account level [ __ ] yes my
cloud servers and full of
[ __ ] of will you help me with our margin
patios and sean simyo like to fire so
the singer of a notary or
new is the dominicus audio brush
video emotions are no that is  and that
had to bottles committees 100 musicians who
oil democratic hunger and media and
towards get cigarettes
station idea to that man who exactly
for pieter claesz well
conical brush is what mr.
tiwari home station i have a look it's
a personal coach armstrong
mix lies maria and discovered the book
partner and that technique you that you
over succeed to may be picked up over the
list okay still young
microbes went to christiaan slang your
operation paris number is quite serious
him there an answer to you diaconu
when we heavily application with
another application and
of your word and euro and soy sauce black
behind the scenes me sometimes as if an action
with the technique liaison mind you to
factors symbolic pile of wood
transfer solutions a cubic
sometimes when you do you want one
shepherds plus 10 again and again accuracy
well
ajax name of your easy or coldest
of getting more not ib office of
ricard closed guide just a girl
must in sparrows that can cancer
foundation nepal the sharia file pointer
to the local group simons
together will nino negri code  Mebius
is five single shades ministers of
place which do may a wish for
and your 6 Arrhenius pockets consolidation
will you quietly marketing sunlight
is indeed nose of new death Pika be
hey in the Balkans you mytouch Arjan
the  qiblah sparta was that I there so long
there no less than
machine dress white ii white people and
advise youtube white powder and vitility
book
just as walls took after meat eats becomes
jos is more is more about how i decide
which you know his little sister and sort of
those things current confusion taxes
after a cover season becomes king of
working with parasites from rockanje
steelers of apple those mini-big bangs
mini-string
the wonders things with in dark scream
clothing maybe knew
charles syndrome a feature semester with
and then yes that kind of grey that is where I
on my we not of every session
further on your score scale of the get
fresh us that we have your hair in extra
showbizzland for young tests seemed
somewhat to
your cake there soon tissue comfort my
finds there a course want think i'm
gonna
to the toilet suffering intense features a
master's degree finance miss bio chain little
brains other coaches breasts
carbohydrate the most very nice to change
and then your technology hang table in
the sauce for business
that word word star remedies aboutaleb
emotions and direction library esmee
grimaud naturally so delicious new
type is
settings and such a  wider the business
otherwise during the race with edgar to
usher that you went to make gif with the
hardware and that no showtime okay wow
but peel around the end socialism
king so drink amsterdam
marinus for change and in i a sign
vector dance your social network
features miami glow bosch en duin
what do you think of he the summer aquino
science what is the basis p-switch there with
you that on how your new software and
game theory massage
to picasa significantly levels mechanical
ultra-high to the single video and audio
just had to be ugly
your codes rapper sjors pastorie business
was not outside cold and yes anyway
already quickly to who the sb salomo was now what
shiva lord south side business and
quasimodo would rather have a mac
m2 citadel really thank god us avatar
church artifacts
by your training in samsung and daan
performance lexi came with shirley java
male voice so an association of keeper
translation sessions
coutinho and lydia ben thomas to word
practically who your own closet but in your
mouth think of that stijn what part of the
source code  is beautiful beautiful potential for
velocity is easier to change
whole expression in terms of suitcase edgar
coach man or shower oil and the source
code legrand harder is the james the name
and that test keep yoga that came in
communication and the interior
this of your guests who if the v&d
go bankrupt who needed oh there in
business ensuite fixed
sitelink a live show I him stand like
objects judge me because introduction in
the clinch well suddenly theory goes with
rick hit him okay was the complete rotterdam
boxing is easy changing harder change
some of that span span of the fogers so
jamie team girl and the now give you
have six people along that fiverr sign
companions
would I a bit of a first object
of grey the the caraïben codex rivals in
the door what is bureau further for the
review on the usa webshop sorry like a
measure like get to work with a taxi
can the great for the things i can do
things don't get support then you have
screen see them surprised minors are
only per ip-address him websites
memetics the experience
that what we know we him builds up and
social ladder unrest girl sorry
the medium rise the million kinds of
features in terms of
see s2 that we have to do
hey business week opinion how that poor
of teams
so there then in eel congrex been for
use on my way social lexicographer qpang
come and see canon the and
then here from kraken his death wish
you with team ot become massage take
then you was cargo thing to the Frisian
politics reasonably narcotic that
germenzeel aquino the seriously had
cerise queen' scores man
music festival and change that the bio
power discotheque or tanks do in
overtime so that business empowering 6 in
seville torch by decisions you is even
more the in terms of family water splashes to that
come traceless
well him historical media tyme amina and
violet work on a lysander tanks badass
a candidate was the public icons
ho as parents anyone stones technique
for the spain knees score hospital
mood grading in just check where there
is a code
why the 10g studying just like my
cherie couple weeks in gps simutrans so that
bacon in the starting to business
a  agent rug and australian koala
this vacancy your syntactically two there is
not seen civil that from the base
of history in the series contacts
divider and sorry push
but i know with lights and take your
time and i not snow over
and I have so conversation paulina
barbary whether there and sometimes it's
not go eraser our big ass and [ __ ] mes
worry
barbie's with kring other information on
a table most sisters measurements
oh what beautiful word of god oh yes a
penguin usa in your resource pack time the
your document already chester out story now
sorry our wanna talk about the cities of
the codebase the technical dept your house yes
and spoke about time
bridge mojo shadow in better than
others
and think munich a big business 30
December
that they
the english tropical carnival people
like this share
oh of modules oil micromax at the
organization and then
nyc after to talk as if I a show tribe
is william more than this this sewer
brother of dreams and that the
governor-general of bradley went so do
you have a lot eyefreight a look at my room
and it is that picasso previous
experience  and stories and just never an
idea for business model with MiBox
machines or something I know him to
so your energy to business i had to
make decisions based upon shortama mount
carmel the time and may be overboard your
business in is make sure thing and
negative impact mango this my shirt
kamlesh messiah per part-up yankee yes
icandy historical to your iphone relations
with a history that kind in gapinge
blinkie a few months jail from which we
come jacket of expensive stand that needed now
that
no which coverages via videos along to just some
noise nation holes
giant figure in Vlissingen
nancy gyan get a can you global
communication
yes i like on many functions of
reengineering our legacy code is me
here at the domain and mainly and belly
communication and I think just a level is
and where you off ar entire interview is there
a went new housing zargar next to
grey hi the sunrise beach orbiter thumbs
up am logistics raisins via just so i
made this property search us then teams
scoured new diy spot and sustainable me
are architectural action photos dry maxi
my fire phone icon
azuri come on  James Tanks with the studio
Ben Banger races ship better module
pro mystery in Adwords havens my
opinion the White Walkers and the codes
Allah only the region Brussels Kisumu
party and they hang semi Geopietra
pieces site linking dessert Frank Force is
the toilet sorry that I see dead room
she decides what and I went for him for
comfort and then my mission that is another a
Mary was playing outside of tanks
there
Sanyo free case for Apple iPhone and
who we Fabio Borini that Caroline Jack and
social and sustainable a lady and then yes
that the way the coach of a bad party
nearby scenario Easter sparrowhawk
weekly participations and apples products
in
jacket racebank just as much about it swift people
were no more they should only be there
would be great as and that those had
researcher and resources
the dik and check-out is there we find
among others at legacy Vermeer oh yes my
website the Samsung gear Uganda
comfort zone Garcia and dot com
mixer and that is in the show notes so if
you then for the heroes and feathers
and tries to see that such as is 2
Drybath began document  a spammy in terms of
material is where the [ __ ] you great do
you think so martijn fabian show with lovely
that your flexpool is in is ideal here
educational program guide to buy cheap
lisa seen for me but at the
podcasting touring other episodes agency
website and ci-dessous radio that we
might be back i come on each of your own
website or region linkedin facebook
twitter of dwars laag channel at sc
video die slash dot com the nursery
molasses team from lesson idea video that this
another village sophie videos license
and the creative commons license to
point five tanks sometimes along